Waiting for the Barbarians is a drama, history film directed by Ciro Guerra.
At an isolated frontier outpost, a colonial magistrate suffers a crisis of conscience when an army colonel arrives looking
to interrogate the locals about an impending uprising, using cruel tactics that horrify the magistrate.
The Magistrate, played by Mark Rylance.
Colonel Joll, played by Johnny Depp.
Officer Mandel, played by Robert Pattinson.
The Girl, played by Gana Bayarsaikhan.
Mai, played by Greta Scacchi.
The Clerk, played by David Dencik.
Waiting for the Barbarians is a 2019 drama film and
English-language directorial debut by Ciro Guerra.
The film is based on the 1980 novel by J.
It stars Mark Rylance, Johnny Depp, Robert Pattinson,
Gana Bayarsaikhan, and Greta Scacchi.
The film premiered at the Venice Film Festival on September 6, 2019.
It was released on August 7, 2020, by Samuel Goldwyn Films.
It received a lukewarm critical response.
The film explores themes of colony, torture, desert, colonization, east asia.
The tone is emotional.